So I haven't said anything about this Taylor Lorenz dark money, Democrat article that came
out. I referenced it, but I haven't talked about it explicitly. And I will on this week's episode
of use from Amanda land. However, it don't matter if you black, white, if you are of Mexican descent,
Asian descent, if you're taking dark money to make video supporting establishment, you're an
op. And when you're doing that to also undermine leftists and other folks who have very valid
concerns, you are an op. I was a victim of this. I thought I was crazy, bro. Within a week of Kamala's
candidacy, there was a concerted effort of all of these black Democrats making videos, musing footage
from like over a year ago to attempt to discredit and to undermine the validity of my voice.
And this picked up like wildfire. And I saw my actual point of view co-opted into something else
by people who look just like me, by people who I'm fighting for every day. I thought I was crazy,
but I know now that I was not, there was a concerted organized effort that had black Democrat
influencers creating content deliberately to discredit and undermine my voice and others.
That's a real thing that happened. And I see people around here talking about, well, you know,
the black creators get the F out of here. You young people need to get your act together and understand
every bag ain't worth getting. You are a continuance of a legacy, a legacy of black journalism,
of black intellectuals that didn't have wifi, that couldn't reach the masses the way that you do.
You have a responsibility. You have a responsibility. Auntie is telling you right now that when you're out
here just trying to get on and getting dark money to do so, it's not going to end well for you.
Course correct now. Course correct now. For the old heads that were taking the money, I'm talking to
you, DL Hughley. Fuck y'all because you're just bought and sold souls. You're going to come and go
and no one's going to remember, but I will because I regarded you as a trusted elder and confidant
and you betrayed me. So I will haunt you in this life and the next. And I'm half Caribbean.
So, you know, I can. You're damn rude.